Joanne N. Bruno

11011 Domain Dr. Austin, TX 78758 (713) 319-5779

joannebruno.com mail@joannebruno.com github.com/joannenbruno

Summary

Multi-disciplinary UX designer and developer with experience in crafting digital products from conceptual ideation to code.

Core Competencies

Languages/Frameworks: HTML5, CSS3, LESS, JavaScript ES6, Angular, Bootstrap Tools: Adobe Illustrator, Sketch, Git/Github, Balsamiq, MS Office Suite

Experience

Senior Software Engineer Software Developer Senior Analyst

October 2017 - Present February 2016 - October 2017

Dell Technologies, Austin, Texas

- Designed and developed software solutions for an internal sales web application with an emphasis on front-end features, brand compliance, and cross-browser compatibility
- Translated wireframes into Angular components, HTML, and CSS/LESS
- Served as a liason between UX and Engineering organizations

Intern

May 2015 - August 2015

Rackspace, San Antonio, Texas

• Developed and implemented data visualization dashboards to provide analytics for product managers across the company

Projects

Lead User Experience Designer

June 2017

June 2017

Keep My Casa, ATX Hack for Change

- Designed user flow and wireframes for a web application aimed at helping Austin residents at risk of losing their homes due to high income property taxes
- Designed logo and branding content for the application
- Translated wireframes to UI prototypes using AngularJS, HTML, CSS, and Angular Material

Lead Designer, Primary Event Organizer

July 2017 - October 2017

DCS Global Hackathon, Dell Technologies

- Designed and implemented all branding logos, print, and marketing material
- Coordinated and led global effort to organize hackathon event for over 500 company employees across 3 countries

Education

B.S. Computer Science, Texas A&M University, College Station, TX Fall 2015

- Information and Intelligent Systems Track
- Department of Visualization Minor in Art

Related Coursework Human Computer Interaction Interactive Information

Designing for the Web Computers and New Media

Honors

Awarded Best Design for ATX Hack For Change Project October 2013 Selected Scholar Grace Hopper Conference of Women in Computing